jobs.lu 2012-11-08

# Privacy Policy - Jobs.lu - Jobs in Luxembourg.

**Overview**    

Jobs.lu has created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following outlines this commitment to users as we want to be able to provide everyone with a user experience that is safe and secure. Jobs.lu wants to ensure, to our best efforts, that any information you give us remains private and are used only for the purposes outlined in this Policy. 

By using the Jobs.lu website, it is understood that you agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

A user can access our website, Jobs.lu (the 'site') and utilise many of our services without providing any information to us at all. Nor do we follow a user's browsing path outside of our site. We do develop summary - not individual \- reports for our recruiters and advertisers. 

This Privacy Policy applies to the Jobs.lu owned website and domain.   
The Jobs.lu website may provide links to third-party websites for your convenience. If you access these links, you will leave the Jobs.lu website. Jobs.lu does not control these sites or their privacy practices. Any exchange of information with unrelated third parties is not covered by this Privacy Policy. We encourage all users to review the Privacy Policy/statement of any third party before submitting personal information.   

**Site Security**   
Jobs.lu is committed to protecting the information you provide us with. To prevent unauthorised access or disclosure of information under our control , Jobs.lu has appropriate security management systems in place to safeguard the information we collect. 

Firewalls, Intrusion Detection and Virus Scanners are used on all parts of the Jobs.lu website. Encryption during transmission is also used on sections of the site where security is particularly important. 

While Jobs.lu makes every effort to protect all personal information, we recognise that unfortunately no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result Jobs.lu cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, you do so at your own risk. 

**Personal Information**   
There are areas of the Jobs.lu website where you can request information, subscribe to marketing materials, enter competitions, register yourself for our online services, request customer support or apply for a job within our organisation. This can involve registering your personal information such as; your name, e-mail address, password, contact details, educational and employment background, and job interest information. The information collected is solely for the purpose of personalising your user experience and for delivering the service(s) that you have signed up for. Once you choose to provide Jobs.lu with personal information, you can be certain that it will only be used to support your relationship with us. 

**Application Information**   
Jobs.lu operates as a platform for jobseekers and recruiters with the tools to enable you to choose the companies and recruitment agencies you would like to speak to when you wish to do so. 

When you make an online application on Jobs.lu your personal information / CV application is received directly by the recruiter. By forwarding your information to that recruiter for the vacancy advertised Jobs.lu understands that it is your decision to disclose this information to a third party and acknowledge that the third party is not covered by the Jobs.lu Privacy Policy. 

**Client Profiles**   
Jobs.lu vacancy advertising clients are given the option to have a profile page on site. This includes information related to their company such as; company logo, contact details, company profile, web address and related links. This information is disclosed for your convenience and information, however if you access some of the links and web addresses disclosed on these pages, you will leave the Jobs.lu website. 

Some Jobs.lu clients are advertised on site under featured employer member pages; which means Jobs.lu host a number of their web pages on our server to provide users with an experience similar to the recruiters own website. 

**Jobs by Email**   
The Jobs by eMail Alert service matches a jobseeker's requirements for employment with the profile of vacancies advertised on our site. For jobseekers who subscribe to this service, you receive an email listing of those jobs which match the criteria you have registered. You can unsubscribe from this service at any time. 

**CVs**   
Jobseekers may decide to register their CV in our database. Users can choose to make their CV searchable for inclusion in our CV database product. This product allows your CV to be viewed by recruiters who have subscribed to this service. It also means that you can attach your CV to your online job application(s). 

We endeavor to grant access to the CV database only to recruiters who agree to abide by our Terms and Conditions. However, should a third party gain access to your CV by evading our security measures, we cannot be held responsible. 

You may remove your CV from our database at any time. However, recruiters who have already accessed your CV may have kept a copy of it in their own files. Please note that we cannot be held responsible for the retention, use, or privacy of your CV in these instances.  

You may review, correct, update or change your **MyJobslu** account profile information or CV at any time. Simply log into your Jobs.lu account, go to your Account Profile or CV, review your account information or CV and, if you wish, edit it with the options provided. You may also delete your CV through this method.  
If you wish to delete your **MyJobslu** account profile information at any time, please contact us at [ jobseekers@jobs.lu](mailto:jobseekers@jobs.ie). An email will be sent to you to confirm that your information has been deleted (save for an archival copy which is not accessible by you or third parties on the Internet). The archival copy is retained indefinitely for audit and record purposes.  
If you wish to revoke your consent to our Privacy Statement, please contact us at at [jobseekers@jobs.lu](mailto:jobseekers@jobs.ie). However, please note that if you do withdraw your consent, you may not be able to use the relevant services and your **MyJobslu** account profile information will be deleted.

**Marketing**   
To provide the best user experience Jobs.lu may invite you to provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests and experiences with our products or services. Providing this additional information is optional. 

**Copyright Statement**   
Copyright is implied irrespective of whether a copyright symbol or a copyright statement is displayed. Content on the Jobs.lu website can be downloaded for personal non-commercial use . Where use of other materials is desired the source must first approve and also be acknowledged. Permission to reproduce the Jobs.lu copyright does not extend to any material on this site which may be the property of a third party. Authorisation to reproduce such material must be obtained from the copyright holders concerned.   

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**   
Jobs.lu reserves the right to change or remove this Privacy Policy at its discretion and will post any new Privacy Policy here. Therefore we would encourage you to visit this area frequently to stay informed.   

**Contact Information**   
Jobs.lu welcomes any comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have reason to believe that Jobs.lu has not adhered to this Privacy Policy, please contact us via email or write to us at the address provided below; and we will make all reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem. 

The Jobs.lu Customer Services Team 

Jobs.ie Ltd  
Unit 1a, Watersedge  
Charlotte Quay  
Dublin 4  
Ireland
